(Seo Ji Hye)
(Go Soo)
(Kim Jae Kyung)
(Yoon Je Moon)
(Reverse)
(This drama is a work of fiction.)
(Characters, places, and events are not real.)
(Children and animals were filmed under production guidelines.)
I know what you're thinking. In your imagination,
you've already killed me...
countless times.
Imagination?
You dying at my hands... That's going to be reality.
It's just a matter of time.
Right.
You're just running away.
Hiding in there, hoping everyone will forget you.
Like a pathetic coward.
Shaking in your boots.
Sure.
I guess you could see it that way.
I guess I'm not smart enough...
because that never occurred to me.
Cut the nonsense.
As long as I'm alive, don't even dream of it.
But the thing is,
that's not how the world works.
You can't be so sure about things.
Because you might be the one who changes.
So don't be so reckless...
Are you saying a girl like me can't do anything?
That you can just stall until I run my mouth, get tired and give up.
Is that your plan?
Are you insane?
Is it starting to sink in now?
From just this?
I promise you.
You are going to die at my hands.
No matter what, I guarantee it.
(The Chase)
(CEO Ryu Jun Ho)
This is the guest list for next month's groundbreaking.
We've selected our allies and are ready to send the invites,
but what should we do about the Vice Chairman?
It seems he called the head of Legal yesterday and gave an order.
He's still trying to dig up dirt on you, sir.
I also heard he ordered a major expansion of the Legal Team.
Well, he's a busy man, isn't he?
So, what should I do about his invitation?
Follow procedure. He's Vice Chairman of the parent company, after all.
Understood.
And one more thing...
Could you find out where the Vice Chairman is right now?
We were bound to meet when the time was right anyway.
What is the meaning of this disrespectful stunt?
My apologies.
I asked the person you were with to give us a moment.
It's just that I feel there's a bit of...
a communication problem between us.
What is there for us to communicate about?
When Architecture was founded,
the agreement was that if it met the three-year revenue goal,
the parent firm would give shares to Architecture.
And the terms of the transfer would be mutually negotiated.
This is clearly stated in its articles of incorporation.
As of this past March,
we hit our target revenue. Now, honour the agreement.
The Chairman has just passed away,
and you have the nerve to bring that up now?
- Vice Chairman... - It may be nothing to you,
but our company is in a state of emergency.
Our founder was found as a pile of ashes overnight.
He was burned to a crisp...
to the point where he was unrecognizable.
And yet,
the police are still...
investigating the cause of the Chairman's death.
So just in case...
that this was no simple accident,
I have to be prepared.
Common sense doesn't apply these days.
- Case in point. - Vice Chairman.
Don't take it personally, all right?
This isn't just me talking.
It's the company's official position.
I'm aware you've been snooping around...
and digging into my past.
It's a pointless exercise for both of us.
You should stop.
Are you giving me an order?
You may be the Vice Chairman...
and my senior in this industry,
but my patience has run out.
From now on,
I can't be held responsible for my actions.
So, Vice Chairman...
I suggest you watch your step.
Why, you little...
Then, I'm glad we've come to an understanding.
I'll see myself out.
Have you ever felt real anxiety?
Like everything could fall apart in an instant...
and that someone could just destroy your life?
Sometimes,
I just want to let it all go.
I'm so exhausted.
It's all too much.
I shouldn't have gone.
That day...
I went somewhere I never should have.
See that over there?
That's where we went.
What? He's here.
Myo Jin, let's go.
Jun Ho!
I missed you.
So, what do you think?
Well?
What's with all this furniture?
Didn't you order the pieces I specified?
What do you mean? It's practically the same.
It's just more expensive.
What on earth?
What happened to all of my specifications?
I told you, I picked out something better.
- You don't like it? - I don't dislike it, it's wrong.
I went over every single detail with the builder and wrote it down,
- and you just threw it all out. - Are you getting mad at me now?
If you hate it so much,
then just throw it all away.
Tear it all out and fill it with what you want.
There. That should make you happy.
Architecture isn't just the shell of a building.
The inside is part of the architecture too.
This may be our villa,
but it's still, undeniably, one of my works in Korea.
You're right.
This is a space just for the two of us.
And I happen to love it just the way it is.
If I love it, shouldn't that be enough for you?
Can't you just drop...
the whole perfectionist act for once?
Please?
You're such a control freak.
Say hi. This is my friend, Myo Jin.
You know who she is, right?
You have a villa like this in every country?
The others are just properties we build and sell,
but not this one.
A certain someone designed it,
so I insisted on having it.
The design?
You mean the one that was half-done by someone else?
Not this again.
Cheers!
Your father is really incredible.
I can't even begin to imagine the scale of his business.
Myo Jin, you seem so fascinated by my dad.
She's always asking me about my dad.
You two...
are so much alike.
- How so? - You both admire my dad.
You're always saying it, Jun Ho. How you want to succeed like him.
And Myo Jin is always saying how much she wants to meet him.
- You do? - I did?
He said he's coming back to Korea soon anyway,
so you can both meet him then.
The three of us can all go see him.
So he's really planning on coming back?
Who knows if he's just talking or if he's serious.
Cheers.
I'm going to run to the restroom.
Myo Jin.
I'm so sorry.
I thought you were Hee Soo.
Oh, no, it's okay. It's my fault.
I shouldn't have borrowed Hee Soo's clothes.
I didn't realise I'd be staying this long.
I'm sorry.
Gosh, I'm not even drunk,
but I can't believe I made a mistake like that.
I am so sorry.
Jun Ho!
Did we finish all the champagne?
Is it all gone?
Hey, that looks great on you.
You should've changed into it sooner.
I guess so.
What are you doing all by yourself? You must be bored.
Come on, let's have another drink.
I'm good for now.
- I'm going to get some fresh air. - Why?
Feeling cooped up?
Then how about we take the yacht out on the water?
No, that's okay. You two enjoy your time together.
Stop.
Why?
I said stop.
What's gotten into you all of a sudden?
Something's off.
Everything feels different.
Are you still on your meds?
Why?
Are you worried?
- What are you doing? Give it to me. - Let go! Are you crazy?
I told you not to up your dosage on your own!
You...
You've really lost it.
What my dad told you...
You haven't forgotten, have you?
All those gifts he gives you...
They don't come for free.
You know that, right?
Get in.
- Sorry? - I said get in. Now.
Is something going on with Hee Soo?
How long have you and Hee Soo been close?
Then you must know.
That she's not an easy person to be close to.
It's just...
we're friends.
It seems like...
Hee Soo is extremely fond of you.
But what about you?
What do you like about her?
You have to understand, Jun Ho.
When women haven't met in a while, they can get a little cranky.
Hee Soo is just...
sensitive than most women, that's all.
You seem to know a lot...
about Hee Soo.
You should go back now.
I'm going to stay out a little longer.
Aren't you curious?
- About what? - If earlier was really an accident.
You must know as well.
That it was no accident.
I'm going back.
I don't want to give anyone the wrong idea.
What wrong idea?
(Recording)
I stole Jun Ho from Hee Soo.
I must have been out of my mind.
I betrayed our friendship...
and just hid it, pretending I didn't know a thing.
But did Hee Soo...
really...
not know anything?
Were you out by the beach?
Yes.
What took you so long?
I guess I was there a little long.
Sounds like you had fun.
- What about Jun Ho? - What?
Jun Ho. I'm asking if you saw him.
I thought I saw him heading toward the beach.
I wouldn't know.
Funny, isn't it?
What? What is?
Everyone's under the same delusion.
They think they can outrun the tide.
But the ocean...
rushes in much faster than you think.
By the time you realise it, it's already too late.
Before you know it,
you're in way over your head.
So you'd better be careful.
You must be tired.
This is yours, isn't it, Myo Jin?
Give it to me.
Hee Soo was right.
- About what? - That you're a great artist.
She told me I should invest in your work now.
Hee Soo was just kidding.
Didn't you know? Hee Soo doesn't joke about that.
Myo Jin. Do you happen to draw people too?
If you need a portrait, ask Hee Soo.
She's a much better artist than I am.
I'm sure she's a great artist,
but I'm...
interested in your art.
One mistake...
was more than enough.
It was so painful I wanted to die. So please, stop toying with me.
- Myo Jin. - I'm not comfortable...
talking to you like this.
You said you went to Seoul this morning, right?
I'm going tomorrow as well.
In fact, my office,
- isn't far from Hee Soo's place. - Please, just stop it.
Mono Architecture.
You can find it on your GPS. Feel free to stop by anytime.
Scum...
To Hee Soo, I was scum. A monster.
I ruined everything, and I stabbed Hee Soo in the back.
Imagine being born in a sandpit in the desert.
Do you know what that's like?
You wash yourself with sand...
and eat sand as if it were food,
just slowly grinding away until you die.
I guess that's what I've become.
Jun Ho betrayed Hee Soo too.
He deceived and destroyed her, just like I did.
We made an irreversible choice,
and Hee Soo died all alone in agony.
Those vile beasts, Ham Myo Jin and Ryu Jun Ho...
We killed Hee Soo.
She must have been so lonely and in so much pain.
Even if it's too late,
I want to pay the price for what we did.
What were you thinking?
It's not a matter of good or bad.
This is nothing more than a personal vanity project.
It's not a traditional "object" form in any way.
Thank you.
You've understood my intention perfectly, sir.
This is for the largest museum in all of Asia right here in Korea.
Not only in scale, but in artistry, technical prowess, and creativity,
it will serve as the benchmark for all of Korean architecture.
With a design like this,
what exactly are you contributing, Mr. Ryu?
Sir.
When most architects begin a new project,
they start by referencing past archetypes.
But as an architect,
- I reject that approach. - Overconfidence is near arrogance.
Constantly referencing past examples...
only leads to an accumulation of derivative work.
Unless we escape this framework,
Korean architecture will ultimately be...
defined by homogenous designs.
You can criticize my work, of course,
but the more that efforts and attempts like mine come together,
I'm confident Korean architecture...
will break free of self-replication.
That's why I chose the concept as Silence for the Sake of Essence.
By eliminating the intrusive functions of conventional buildings,
we can focus on its contents, the people, the music,
and on faithfully capturing the very essence of life itself.
(HGA Distribution)
Spit it out, you jerk!
What did I do that was so wrong?
Is taking a nap after lunch a capital offence?
Besides, you had one of the others do my work for me anyway.
So in the end, it's not like I caused any real trouble,
is what I'm saying.
Gosh, this jerk sure loves to hear himself talk.
Hey, you beat the crap out of the site manager for no reason,
and you say that's not wrong? Then what is?
That jerk of a manager has it in for me.
He's always on my back,
picking a fight over every little thing.
What was I supposed to do?
A person's patience has a limit.
- Doesn't it? - A limit? Are you a credit card?
A limit? For you?
Look at this jerk, dumber than me.
Listen to him think he's hot stuff.
Hey! You got paid, so just do your job.
While everyone else is working, you're just passed out asleep.
You think you can just beat him up, you scum?
You want a piece of me?
Okay? I would just...
Did everything I told you go in one ear and out the other?
What are you talking about?
An idiot with a bad memory. That's why he always makes trouble.
When you act like a bum...
in a foreign country, you make us Joseonjok look bad.
Didn't I tell you that?
The reason we Joseonjok get treated like nonsense wherever we go...
is because of idiots like him making trouble for everyone.
Didn't I tell you that? Does none of this ring a bell?
- I remember. - I remember.
- I remember. - What?
So you remember, and you did it anyway?
So then, because of you,
all of us Joseonjok are going to get a bad name again.
- How will you take responsibility? - Boss, I was wrong.
From now on, I won't eat, and I won't even work out.
I swear I'll do nothing but work.
That idiot.
Make him think about what he's done until I give the word.
Boss! Please, have mercy.
I was wrong! Please, just spare me this once.
Boss!
- Spare me! - Shut it!
The way you're screaming, it sounds like you're going to your execution.
Boss!
Something terrible's happened. Hae Sik...
got beaten up by some thugs and was rushed to the hospital.
Wait, who?
Your brother, Boss. Hae Sik.
This is so unfair.
I even got disciplined at work today...
and now this? What did I do to deserve this?
Are you sure that's the whole story?
- You really did nothing wrong? - Boss, you know me better.
Have you ever seen me cause trouble anywhere?
Because of me,
have our people...
lost face even once?
You see the state I'm in,
and you still don't believe your own brother?
Do you remember where it was?
I don't know where the guys who did this to me are,
but I know where to find the guy who drugged our drinks.
My friend gets out of the hospital tomorrow,
so I can ask him then.
Then why didn't you tell me any of this before?
I know you just got back from a long-awaited trip home.
It's not exactly something to brag about, is it?
It's bad enough getting beat up in a foreign country.
If word gets out that I'm some pathetic loser,
- what about my reputation? - Your reputation?
Then out of all those guys, why'd you get beat up the worst?
If I don't look out for our guys, who will?
You think I wanted to get beat up like this?
Gosh, it hurts.
All right.
Look at the state of you.
(Jongdo Construction Union)
Boss, who's that wench shacking up with now?
She's bound to contact you again soon, right?
When she does, just signal me. I'll take care of the rest...
Why do you always say the same thing every time you show up?
You're like a broken record.
If she shows up here,
and I give you a heads-up,
- ...you'll handle it, right? - You just sit back...
and enjoy the spoils, Boss.
What's your angle?
What?
Why drag me into something you can do on your own?
- What are you talking about? - You want me to spell it out?
If that kid ends up dead,
you'd be the one who did it,
but I'd have her blood on my hands.
If you were to act alone,
since I...
would know it was your doing,
you'd be afraid I'd retaliate. And after her,
you'd have to get rid of me next.
So you were probably wondering what to do.
Quite the dilemma for you.
That's why from the very beginning,
you've been trying to drag me into this.
Boss, wait, you've got it all wrong...
You, pull a stunt that transparent?
A guy who crawled his way up from a construction site hustler...
to a chauffeur for a rich family?
Bring me money!
I don't care what your scheme is! I'll do whatever you want!
Have you already forgotten...
what it takes to get me on board?
If you come to me empty-handed and try to pull this crap again,
it won't be her.
You'll be the first to die by my hand.
You got it? Now, get lost.
You're tiring me out.
You're still up?
Are you okay?
I have something to ask you.
And I need you to be honest with me.
Okay.
What is it?
It's about Choi Hee Soo.
Why haven't you told me about your relationship with Hee Soo?
- Myo Jin... - You said you barely knew her...
How could you...
How could you lie to me like that?
It's too much for you to hear while you're still recovering.
That you abandoned Hee Soo, your girlfriend,
and that I betrayed my friend...
That's what's "too much" for me?
No.
That's something I absolutely need to know.
- Myo Jin. - You hid it, scared I'd be shocked,
and that you'd tell me everything once I recovered?
Were you just going to say Hee Soo, abandoned by scum like you and me,
died in an accident, just gone? Is that it?
I'm sorry.
I was selfish.
But I didn't hide it on purpose.
How could I possibly hide it?
You were going to remember everything eventually.
It was hard for me to talk about,
and I knew it would be hard for you to hear,
so I guess I wanted to put it off for as long as I could.
It's all my fault.
Hee Soo was struggling.
She said people were just using her. That she was all alone.
The only people she trusted were you and me.
Hee Soo was already on the edge.
Darn, every time I try something, it all goes sideways.
What happened to Hee Soo?
The investigation is still ongoing. We'll find out in time.
What was I doing there that day?
Like Detective Woo said,
I can't remember why my accident happened...
near the vacation home, no matter how hard I try.
I thought none of Choi Hee Soo's accounts were left.
The forensics team had a tough time with it.
A young US citizen with no social media?
Does that make any sense?
She had them. Someone must have deleted them.
Maybe she deleted them herself.
They were deleted after the incident.
No way.
Wait. Choi Hee Soo and Ham Myo Jin knew each other?
They were friends?
Hey, what do you make of this?
This is an engagement photo.
Choi Hee Soo and Ryu Jun Ho?
Gosh, this Ham Myo Jin woman gives me the creeps.
She pretended to know nothing.
This was the reason.
After Choi Hee Soo died in an accident,
her "friend," Ham Myo Jin, swooped in and took her place?
The way she's sticking to this cliche story,
you almost have to wonder if she really did lose her memory.
I know you're busy, so thank you for making time for me.
I hope you'll find everything to your liking.
I've made reservations at a special place for dinner.
When have your plans ever been anything but special?
It's looking like Oh Sang Il...
is going to be appointed head of the judge committee.
The other members are all unanimously recommending him.
It's not just me. Everyone in our industry is on edge.
On edge? There's no need for that.
After all, with this project,
there are only a handful of companies that can handle it.
I will ensure it's a success, no matter what.
I know very well what you're capable of.
But there is something.
Do you happen to know someone named Ryu Jun Ho?
He's still a bit green, but he's got the fundamentals down.
He hasn't been back in the country for long,
but the projects he's worked on have been decent.
Why do you ask?
I heard he paid a secret visit to Oh Sang Il.
The timing's a bit suspicious, don't you think?
He's not even eligible to apply with no domestic experience.
Those requirements have already been made public.
You know they're announcing committee members next week, right?
Yes, Assemblyman.
At that time,
a revised clause will be announced as well.
Oh Sang Il apparently requested it himself.
He wants a merit-based review, without barriers or discrimination.
Sounds just like something Oh Sang Il would say.
Still, I wouldn't get too complacent if I were you.
There's always a loophole somewhere.
I'm so sorry.
For just showing up like this during your break.
Like your memories, you mean?
Before he met me, Jun Ho was already engaged.
And I was friends with her.
I don't know why I did it,
but I found out that I'm the one who stole him from her.
I went through all that, seeking a profound truth.
And all I found out...
is what a horrible person I am.
Doctor...
Is there any point in continuing with this therapy?
Tell me.
Tell me what's really on your mind, Myo Jin.
I'm scared.
I'm in so much pain right now I feel like I could die.
But what if there's more?
- If there really is, I... - That's for you to decide, Myo Jin.
It always has been.
I've only been here to help, in my own small way.
Human memory gets distorted.
No one's memory stays perfectly intact.
Distorted?
Time changes everything.
And memories are no exception.
In the case of a major accident like the one you had,
you have to be even more careful when assessing the situation.
To steal your friend's boyfriend and then say you don't know why...
That's a form of avoidance. Or it's an excuse.
- Doctor, it really is not... - I know. It's neither of those.
As your doctor, the Myo Jin I've come to know...
genuinely doesn't know why she did what she did.
- Then what is it? - I know this is hard,
but try to be more patient.
Because the truth...
might be different from what you think it is.
Could that really be true?
We'll have to wait and see.
You're already making great progress.
(Jigu Electronics)
No, that's a lie.
On that day, this jerk brought us drinks and food himself.
What's he talking about? That idiot.
So he wouldn't leave a trail. He didn't take a card, only cash.
He took another cut handing us over to those thugs, double-dipping.
I've run this bar my whole life, and now I'm a human trafficker.
Sir.
Relax. No one's going to eat you alive.
You can lose the scowl.
It's messing up your handsome face.
You'd think that we're the ones here to shake you down.
All right, that's enough.
If you're that bored, go get wasted somewhere else.
What? Want me to recommend a place?
You're a real character.
What?
What are you, their fixer?
You came here to threaten me, is that it?
All right, fine.
I'm going to step into the kitchen for a minute.
I have to prep for the dinner service.
If you're still here when I'm back, pulling this nonsense,
then I can't be responsible for what happens.
- That idiot. - Take this "guest" outside.
You're making a huge mistake. You hear me?
For a business owner, you're so darn clueless.
Why that little...
Darn!
Make another sound, and I'll snap your arm right off.
Why is it you Korean scums never listen when I ask nicely?
Do I need to repeat what I want to know?
No, I'll talk. I'll tell you everything.
This is just for show.
Yes.
Weird. You Korean guys...
(Repentance)
Open your eyes. Anyone with their eyes closed dies.
Where are we?
Today, I've got a special job for you.
Teach this little punk a lesson.
He's a scumbag who drugged our guy and stole his money.
The boss gave the okay, so do whatever you want with him.
Is he one of our guys?
- No, he's a thug from Korea. - So we can do whatever we want?
- Do whatever you want. I'm out. - No, wait.
Wait, where are you going?
Please, save me!
Let go of me, you jerk!
Sir!
Pinky! This little punk...
is that foreman's younger brother who gives you a hard time.
Sir... Sir!
Well, nice to meet you, you scum.
Today, I'm going to beat all the fat right out of your gut.
You sure took your sweet time. I seriously thought I was a goner.
I had to pull every string I have just to track this down.
Privacy laws are no joke these days. If you get caught, you're done for.
Also, because of this whole thing,
I should be billing for the business I lost at my shop...
Are you absolutely sure it's Lee Jong Su?
How many times do I have to say it? I've been doing this for 30 years.
Trust me.
Right. Take this before I forget.
I fixed it, so it should work perfectly now.
Thank you.
So what's your main gig? The electronics shop or private eye?
Dongdae Police Station, Violent Crimes Unit one.
I was the top ace in the entire division.
So what happened?
Let's just say I messed up and got fired.
How was I supposed to know where that money came from?
After being unemployed for about two years,
my wife took the kids and left me.
But she won't grant me a divorce. It's driving me crazy. Darn it.
So you got fired for taking a bribe?
Hey! A bribe? Don't be ridiculous!
You don't need to know the details.
Hey!
That's him. That's our guy.
He's leaving right now.
You've seen this in the movies, right?
- We're about to do the best part. - The best part?
The good guys go after the bad guy.
But why is this car so slow?
We're going to lose him at this rate.
Lose him? We're only this close because I'm the one driving.
Gosh, Lee Jong Su... That jerk.
So what exactly are we supposed to find out from this guy?
I can't do my job if I don't know what's going on.
I can't tell you yet.
You can't tell me? I'm the one you hired!
You haven't forgotten who I am, have you?
It's not that.
- It's because I don't know either. - What? You don't know the reason?
It looked like someone had something on Hee Soo.
I asked her what it was, but she would never tell me.
But Choi Hee Soo is dead.
We must get the truth from him, the man who blackmailed her.
You kidding? You think a guy like that will just talk?
There's no other way. I have to find out, no matter what.
Now that Choi Hee Soo is dead,
- why find that out now? - The day Lee Jong Su...
came to the studio,
they both avoided me.
Hey! Did I ask you for this pathetic amount of money?
Who are you to be giving me money?
- Hey! Who are you? - No! Myo Jin, don't!
Don't. Just don't.
- Hee Soo! - It's fine. I'll call you.
Go.
Choi Hee Soo and Lee Jong Su? Why would they do that?
He has to know what the reason was.
Considering they both avoided me,
- I must be involved in this. - This had better be worth it.
I'm getting out here.
Did he go up?
- He stopped on the second floor. - Okay, we need to hurry. Let's go!
Quick, hide over here! We can't let him spot us!
But what's the plan? We can't just follow him blindly.
He's finishing up his conversation and heading inside.
Judging by the photo of him at the entrance,
I'd say he's the owner.
What's this? A wine bar? You've got to be kidding me.
Seriously,
where did that jerk get all this money?
So what are we supposed to do now?
Here, take this.
What is this?
It's a cloning kit. All you have to do is plug this in,
and a light on the kit will turn on and start copying.
Even with a lot of data, a phone only takes one minute.
Actually, no, wait. Is it two minutes?
- Anyway, it's simple, right? - You want me to do it to his phone?
By myself? Right now?
If you want to know about someone, you look at their phone.
Their entire life is in there.
But what if I get caught?
I can't do this.
You think you can ask that jerk, "Why did you blackmail my friend?"
You think he's just going to say, "Well, you see, the truth is?"
This is the only way to find out what that jerk was plotting!
What am I supposed to do?
First, find that guy's office. Come on, hurry!
- Go on! Hurry. - But...
Welcome.
This way, please.
Excuse me. Where can I find the owner?
He's with a client right now. Should I interrupt if it's urgent?
No, it's okay. I can just wait until he's finished.
All right. Let me know when you're ready to order.
You're looking even better than last time.
Really? I guess my money was well spent.
I look forward to your favourable decision.
Of course I'll invest.
Thanks to you, this time should go smoothly too.
Hey! Who's the owner here? Get out here, now!
- Is it you? You? - Excuse me, sir. May I help you?
I see.
- So it's you. - Oh, my gosh!
You're the jerk who made my wife divorce me!
What lies did you tell her to make her serve me divorce papers?
You scum!
Sir, you can't be doing this here. Please, calm down first.
Let's go over there and discuss this calmly.
Calmly? You want me to be calm?
Don't give me that "calmly" nonsense!
You think I'm your customer? I'm your customer's husband!
The husband of the customer you're messing with, you scum!
- What? - What are you doing? Let go of him!
You slept with my wife, didn't you? You think I wouldn't find out?
See? You can't even deny it! You messed with the wrong guy!
How many times? I asked, how many times?
So you really did it?
My wife's eyes were so bloodshot that I took her to the doctor,
and they said she's a wine-aholic, you jerk!
Look, just let go of me and we can talk!
- What're you doing? Get him off me. - Yes, sir.
What is wrong with you?
Your plan was to ruin me, then take my wife and my money.
Think you can get away with that? You've messed with the wrong guy!
What are you talking about? Darn it.
Hey, let go of me! I'll have all of you thrown in jail!
Let go!
Hurry.
- Oh, no, what do I do? - Gosh, what a terrible day.
Just my luck... Some crazy jerk has to show up.
Hey! Where do you think you're going?
Hey, you! You slept with my wife, didn't you?
Did you think I wouldn't find out? Look at him! He can't even deny it!
Hurry.
How many times? I asked, how many times?
So you really did it? Hey..
You scum!
Who are you?
What?
I...
You've got a lot of nerve showing up here.
Let me go! Let go of me! Let me...
Sir! He's a cop!
- What? - You're all dead! Assaulting a cop?
- What? Darn! - What are you doing? Let go!
Mister!
Mister, are you all right?
Wang Gi Cheol, that scum!
We can't let that jerk get away!
Right.
Darn it!
Hey, Lee Jong Su!
Hey! Wait a minute!
Darn!
- Darn it! - I have a question for you!
It'll only take a second!
Darn!
Call 911!
Look...
You vicious wench.
Wasn't killing those two...
enough?
You can just stop now.
This revenge of yours.
(Reverse)
Once we see what they exchanged, we'll have our answer.
You killed my parents?
I didn't think you'd find out this fast.
So what should I do?
- Stop him. - You did the Jebudo explosion?
Yeah, well, that's all a bunch of bullshit.
You don't need to know. It'll only put us both in danger.
Thanks to you, I figured it out. What's been going on behind my back.
That there's someone else targeting Ham Myo Jin...
other than us?